I am responsible,
because I am not vigilant.
Valda received 1 yellow here in the hall
today.
I'm late,
bro.
I heard the trade seems to close for half a day and I need to run.
It's alcohol,
please.
30 count bro.
Water,
soap and a little lip.
There are many people who end up making the salespeople and
employees clean the window in a not-so-professional way to save money.
Money is also on.
I can't keep marking this,
man.
I have to create some idea.
And yesterday I was looking at 1 Instagram and I
saw 1 product of cleaning beauty salon chair barber,
I thought,
coal miner is there all the time,
all the time,
bro cut a hair,
go in another,
the person comes from football.
A guy who's a mechanic wears a cooler shirt.
He's sitting in that same chair.
Create your own opportunity.
Hand.
Don't wait for things to happen,
are you okay?
Hi,
all good.
He who is responsible.
Yes,
I'm from surveillance.
Oh, that's cool.
I brought a reagent here so I could see the quality of your chairs.
It's okay,
I can start.
You take care of your salon.
You know who isn't taking care of their customers?
In fact,
I'm not surveillance.
What I do are chair maintenance.
Forgive me, okay?
It's our job.
Speak, brother,
you who are in charge there,
folks,
here I received a report and I was talking to the person in charge there,
brother.
Beauty,
the guy comes to the barbershop here now
the guy let me make some chairs and a couch,
it's giving good
Education
caraca mano go get me a beard deal here now uncle caraca mano,
the guy gave a legal deal on my beard,
I'm in a gradient mano,
now I'm guessing where mano for the 1st time in line at's.
Our Face,
how long has I not ordered 1 Mac?
All right, girl.